Fabio Damian Argañaraz Azua

Computer Engineer, Full Stack Web Developer and Professor.

Full Stack Developer with 4 years of experience and a solid background in web development and teaching. Proficient with tools and technologies such as Node, React, Redux, Typescript, JavaScript, Jest and many others. Strong skills with Mongo DB and PostgreSQL. Works as a teacher in recognized institutions, and stands out in communication skills, focusing on agile development, and mastering development technologies.



ing.fabio.arg@gmail.com

(+54) 388 5733294

San Salvador de Jujuy, Argentina

CUIL: 20-33676737-8

linkedin.com/in/FabioDrizZt

github.com/FabioDrizZt



WORK EXPERIENCE

Professor FrontEnd Development. Argentina Programa 4.0 - UNTREF

05/2023 - Present

Argentina

- · Creation of didactic material and practical exercises.
- Evaluation and monitoring of student progress.
- HTML+CSS+JavaScript+git+React+Routing

Professor BackEnd and FrontEnd Development.Digital Mind

05/2022 - Present

Cordoba, Argentina

- Creation of didactic material and practical exercises.
- Evaluation and monitoring of student progress.
- git+PHP+MySQL+Laravel & HTML+CSS+JS+React+Jest+RTL

Professor BackEnd and FrontEnd Development.Next U

05/2022 - Present

Bogota, Colombia

- Support in the design and development of updated curricula.
- Continuous feedback and technical assistance to students.

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer Upwork, Fiverr, PeoplePerHour

01/2022 - Present

Remote

- Completed multiple freelance projects.
- Developed web applications using technologies such as React, Redux, Node.js, Express, and MongoDB.
- Collaborated with clients to understand their requirements and deliver high-quality solutions.
- Managed project timelines, communicated effectively, and delivered projects on time and within budget.

Professor "Web Programming", "Models and Simulation", "Computer Science" and "Fundamentals of Artificial Intelligence". UCSE-DASS

09/2017 - Present

Jujuy, Argentina

- Development of curricula and teaching materials.
- Advice and guidance to students on projects and practical work.

Full Stack Web Developer Zero Q

05/2021 - 12/2021

Santiago, Chile

- Participation in the development of web applications using technologies such as React, Redux, Node.js, Express and MongoDB.
- Collaboration in the design and implementation of frontend and backend solutions.
- Work in an agile team following Scrum methodologies.

SKILLS



PROYECTOS PERSONALES

Mobile e-wallet (10/2020)

 Development of Henry Bank, a mobile virtual wallet, using React Native and Microservices.

Web e-commerce (09/2020)

 Development of Sports Store, a fictitious sports store, with PERN technology.

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

Computer Engineering

National University of Jujuy (UNJu)

02/2009 - 12/2015

Medal for the best average in Computer Engineering

Full Stack Web Developer

HENRY soyhenry.com

06/2020 - 10/2020

 Stack: - HTML5 - CSS - Javascript - React + Redux - Node (Express, Sequelize, JWT) - PostgreSQL

LANGUAGES

Spanish English

Full Professional Competence